senorwooly.com 2019-05-18

# Señor Wooly

Señor Wooly, LLC is committed to keeping all users’ personal information safe and private. The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide users of our website with information regarding the type of personal information we collect, and how it is used. For detailed information about privacy provisions applicable to children/minors, please see the section beginning with **Children’s Privacy**.

#### Your consent

By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy and our terms and conditions. This policy was last modified on December 12, 2018 and governs the use of our website and information associated with the purchase of products through our website. We encourage you to refer to this policy periodically so that you understand our current privacy policies.

#### What information do we collect?

  * We collect information from you when you register on the website, place an order, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another website feature.
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, name of school where you work, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously. 
  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other website features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other website feature.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes.
  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please send us an email at senorwooly@senorwooly.com with the subject line “Unsubscribe”.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All information you supply, including but not limited to sensitive information like login credentials and credit information, is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We do not store any credit card information.

In addition, we ensure that all data transactions and transfers with our customers are encrypted.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the website's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use two types of cookies—session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for the duration of time you have your internet browser open when you visit our site and are used for functions such as remembering and processing items in your shopping cart. Persistent cookies do not disappear when you exit your browser, but instead persist each time you visit our website. These cookies are used to help us better understand your preferences based on previous or current website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interaction so that we can offer better website experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your website experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting Customer Service.

#### Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. The term "outside parties" does not include Señor Wooly, LLC. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

#### How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions or other information that you have provided to us, please click “Unsubscribe” at the top of the e-mail.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, please send us a request via e-mail. Please note that we may continue to maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for internal record keeping purposes.

#### Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our website. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. These linked websites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, Señor Wooly LLC seeks to protect the integrity of our website and welcomes any feedback about these linked websites (including if a specific link does not work).

#### Changes to our policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this “Señor Wooly Privacy Policy” page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

#### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code §§ 1798.83-.84 provide users that are California residents with a right to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we may share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As noted above, we do not currently provide personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

#### Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy or this policy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue by contacting us via phone at (224) 935-3088 or by mail at Señor Wooly, LLC, P.O. Box 903, Skokie, IL 60076.

#### Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please visit our Terms and Conditions section, which establishes use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Children’s Privacy

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and other laws have been established to protect the privacy of minors. At Señor Wooly, LLC, we take the privacy rights of our users, especially children, very seriously, and abide by all federal and state laws and guidelines regarding youth privacy. The following outlines our general children’s privacy guidelines:

Señor Wooly, LLC exists to serve educators, parents and students and strives to provide a safe, positive experience for children. To ensure this, we adhere to the following policies:

  * We do not knowingly collect online contact information directly from children ages 13 and younger.
  * We do not distribute any personally identifiable information about children to third parties.
  * We do not allow students to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.
  * We do not use the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to entice children to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

Señor Wooly, LLC provides an online service marketed towards educators. The services we provide to students/minors are solely for the use and benefit of their school, and for no other commercial purpose. To that end, COPPA allows the school of the student/minor to act as the parent’s agent, and can consent to the collection of kid’s information on the parent’s behalf. 

##### What information do you collect from students/minors?

We do not collect any personal information from students under the umbrella of a teacher account with the exception of first name, the first letter of the last name, and the school they attend.  Teachers have the option of changing a setting in order to allow for the input of students’ last names.  Teachers will only enable this option if the school district has given consent to do so. If the teacher, school, or school district wishes to delete these last names, they can do so by changing the setting back to last name initial only, after which all full last names will be permanently deleted from the server.  

This information is gathered from the students directly, and not through the use of cookies. This information will only be used by their teacher in order to distinguish them from their classmates. **This information will never be disclosed to third parties for any reason.**

##### How do we use this personal information?

Señor Wooly, LLC never directly uses the personal information provided by students/minors. Only teachers or their agents use the information, to distinguish between students in their class.

##### Does Señor Wooly, LLC use or share the information for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the online services requested by the school? For instance, does Señor Wooly, LLC use the students’ personal information in connection with online behavioral advertising, or building use profiles for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the online service?

No.

##### Does Señor Wooly, LLC enable the school to review and have deleted the personal information collected from their students?

Yes, at any time.

##### What measures does Señor Wooly, LLC take to protect the security, confidentiality, and integrity of the personal information that it collects?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

##### What are Señor Wooly, LLC’s data retention and deletion policies for children’s personal information?

All information provided by children is kept under the umbrella account of their teacher. The teacher can, at any time, delete the student from their umbrella account, which will erase all personal information from Señor Wooly, LLC servers. That said, Señor Wooly, LLC can also delete students’ personal information. This can be requested by sending a notice of the request to Señor Wooly, LLC at senorwooly@senorwooly.com. Such request must include the name, teacher’s name, and school of the minor making the request and the posted information, material and content on the website they are requesting to have removed. Upon receipt of such a request, Señor Wooly, LLC will remove material, information, and content posted on the website, including answers, results, scores, and other information provided as part of the use of programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests on the website.

##### Parental Rights

Señor Wooly, LLC will never require a child to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity. At any time, parents can review their child’s personal information, direct us to delete it, and refuse to allow any further collection of use of the child’s information. 

Señor Wooly, LLC believes there is no information on its website which is inappropriate or objectionable for viewing by children. 

##### On-Line Eraser for Minors In California

California law provides for the ability of minors that are registered users of the website to request and obtain removal of material, information, and content posted on the website. Registered users 17 years of age or younger who are California residents, may request Señor Wooly, LLC to remove their own posted content on the website by sending a notice of the request to Señor Wooly, LLC at senorwooly@senorwooly.com. Such request must include the name, teacher’s name, and school of the minor making the request and the posted information, material and content on the website they are requesting to have removed. Upon receipt of such a request, Señor Wooly, LLC will remove material, information, and content posted on the website, including answers, results, scores, and other information provided as part of the use of programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests on the website. Please note that in complying with such a request, the posted information, material, and content will no longer be visible to other users of the website or public, including teachers, schools, and school officials who have set up the programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests as part of a school program or class activity. The material, information, and content will not be deleted from the Señor Wooly, LLC server; it will just no longer be visible or accessible by other users or the general public. There are exceptions to complying to the request where the posted information, material, and content will not be removed from visibility to or access by other users, such as where federal or state law requires Señor Wooly, LLC or its third parties to maintain the information, material, and content, the information, material, and content is stored on or posted to the Señor Wooly, LLC website by a third party, the information, material, and content is provided and maintained anonymously, the minor fails to follow the instructions regarding removal, or the minor has received compensation or other consideration for providing the information, material, and content.
